heb.com 2007-12-10

# Privacy Policy

Notice: We collect personal information on this site. To learn more about how we use your information, please read our privacy policy. **

Online Privacy and Security

**

H.E. Butt Grocery Company (H-E-B) recognizes the importance of privacy to our customers and visitors to our Web site (the "site") and will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information that you provide to us. We value your trust and respect. Personal information is information about you that is not publicly available and can identify you, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and phone number. We only collect the information you choose to give us in order to better serve you. Other information collected about you from other parts of H-E-B's business, such as stores or pharmacy operations, may be regulated differently and/or subject to different privacy practices. 

**What personal information do we collect?**  
We collect and store information when you choose to subscribe to the H-E-B online e-newsletters. This may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal or preference information you may provide to us.

We collect billing and shipping information for purchases made with a credit  
or debit card. This may include your name, your billing address, the card  
type, number, and expiration date. We also collect information that allows us  
to ship your order including the name, address, and telephone number of the  
intended recipient.

H-E-B may conduct surveys and contests either from our Web site in conjunction with other media or in our H-E-B stores. If you choose to participate, we may request your name, mailing address, or other personal information.

Customers may submit comments from our Web site. Personal information may be requested such as your name, phone number, or other contact information.

We collect certain technical information from your computer during your visit to our Web site. This may include your computer's operating system and browser type. When you visit our Web site, you will be assigned a "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit our Web site and allow us to enhance your online experience. Most Internet browsers permit you to erase or block cookies. Refer to your browser instructions to assist you in this process, although doing so may affect your ability to use the site to its maximum benefit. 

**How do we use your personal information?**

  * H-E-B e-newsletter subscriptions
  * Notice of special promotions or events
  * Online ads
  * Surveys and contests
  * Employment applications
  * Verification of credit card information
  * Billing and order confirmation
  * Customizing your shopping experience
  * Measuring and improving the effectiveness of our websites

When you contact our service representatives, we may ask for personal information in order to verify your identity. We may share personal customer information with third parties with whom we have contracted to perform services or functions on our behalf whose activities are subject to the terms of this privacy policy. 

H-E-B collects, stores, and uses aggregate data that does not contain personally identifiable information. This aggregated data may be shared with and used by third parties in order to help us and our business partners better serve and understand our customers.

**How can I access, modify, and/or delete my information?**  
You may at any time review, edit, and/or remove from our database any information we maintain on you by performing that task online or by contacting us directly. We will promptly comply with any request to review, edit, or remove your information.

**What choices do you have?**  
You can choose to not provide personal information or only limited information. 

You can choose to subscribe only to certain services offered by H-E-B. 

If you subscribe to the H-E-B e-newsletters or other services, you may choose to unsubscribe at anytime. 

**What about the privacy rights of children?**  
We are committed to protecting children's privacy. We do not and will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. If any data entry by a visitor indicates that such visitor is under the age of 13 years, all data from that visitor is promptly deleted from our system. If a child under 13 years of age wants to participate on our Web site, we encourage the child's parents to participate in his or her experience on our site. We welcome family participation. 

**What security measures are in place with respect to my information?**  
You transmit information to us at your own risk. However, if your browser is properly configured and your computer is operating properly, you may choose to transmit encrypted information to us using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

All information received is stored in a secure database protected by multiple firewalls and other security measures.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect. 

Internally, H-E-B restricts consumer information under our control to those persons who have a need to know such information. 

**Links to other Web sites**  
H-E-B may provide links to non-H-E-B Web sites. These sites are not under the control of H-E-B, and H-E-B is not responsible for the content or the information collection practices of these Web sites. You may want to review the privacy policies of these sites and how they collect and use personal information. 

**Your consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to H-E-B's use of personally identifiable information about you as set forth in this privacy policy. If you do not agree with this privacy policy or any of its terms, you may choose to not use our site. This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. H-E-B reserves the right to amend this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy policy via postings on our site. Your continued use of our Web site following the posting of changes or amendments to this privacy policy constitutes acceptance of those changes and amendments. 

**If you have any other questions or comments**  
You may contact us with any other questions or comments at:

**Direct Mail Address:**  
H.E. Butt Grocery Company  
Attention: Privacy Office  
P.O. Box 839999  
San Antonio, TX 78283-3999

**E-Mail Address:**  

**Telephone:**  
_Contact the Privacy Office_  
San Antonio, Texas 210-938-4923  
Outside of San Antonio 866-432-4318

_Contact Customer Relations_  
San Antonio, Texas 210-938-8357  
Outside of San Antonio 800-432-3113

**Policy Revisions and Updates**  
This privacy policy will continue to be reviewed and revised as changes occur in H-E-B business and technology or to laws that affect this policy. All information collected is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time of use. Changes will be posted on this site with an updated effective date. Please check our Web site periodically to see the current policy. 

Last Revision Date: December 1, 2003
